that issue right there
I'm hoping this helps with the sounds
because I hate listening to videos with
bad sound or music in the background
I was just on Facebook and in this
career spoons with I'm recently part of
it gets really participated so anyway
someone posted someone's cool website
and was looking at their website and
then also their Facebook profile and a
post from a human who was talking about
their changing body and coming to terms
with how the body is changing getting
ever more sick and having organs shut
down and they were talking about
specifically getting the catheter and
the emotions and stuff that brought up
and they brought up stuff in me a big
piece of which is to share my vision or
what I want to create and it's like the
what isn't really that importance but
the what is a app that helps us get our
health in our hands helps us be better
advocates for ourselves helps us walk
into appointments with our entire
communities behind us of scientific
information of experiencing our bodies
of taking the data on the experiments
for all in willingly or unwillingly
because we're all that's how we
collectively get to our individual
optimal health whatever that means to
the individual is by doing it together
so that's like the what is a health care
app designed with and for people with
health challenges not
for the 99% not for the people who I
don't even know what those statistics
are how many people have disabilities
how many people are in chronic pain or
have their brain change have something
about their physical or mental body that
doesn't work in society because the
world I want to create is the world that
everybody fits into I know from my
experience having brain tumors having my
brain change having experiement
experiencing chronic pain and chronic
exhaustion that it has given me
something it has given me patients still
on that learning process but it's given
me compassion and a new way of looking
at the world it's helped me value my
emotions in my body more so than what
identified out with before which was
intellectual and smart and I'm still
intellectual and smart and still value
those things but can see where they were
holding me back and where they hold
society back where we can use them and
where we need to move beyond them and in
our society that is capitalistic an
ableist and racist in all of these
limitations
it's our uniqueness it's where we're
different it's where we struggle and
where we're awesome and where our unique
place that is amazing and what we have
to offer each other and the world I want
to create is the tools to be able to
harness that the tools to be able to
bring the right people together the
tools to be able to find your place in
the world no matter what your
limitations and talents and these
desires are that we create the tools for
the diversity that exists on this planet
and one of the most
diverse things we have is our difference
in ability are different in our
cognitive ability and every different
kind of intelligence the difference in
our physical ability in all different
kinds of ways that we move and use our
bodies and in all different ways that we
like metabolize and like we are diverse
not just in our outward appearance but
also in our internal workings and the
way that our minds work and we're
supposed to have that diversity because
that's how we get to live better lives
is by allowing other people to live
better lives I can't function at
society's level but I can foresee invent
discover I don't even know where it is
ways to use knowledge with technology so
that I don't have to do that mental work
in the future like okay I can't do the
basic process of picking out a meal plan
and going grocery shopping and a lot of
that is really difficult and is and
becomes more and more difficult as my
body changes and my brain more changes
having tools to be able to do that like
right so here's the meal plan for the
week there's 10,000 people in Vancouver
that are eating this meal plan so the
groceries are cheap they're delivered to
your neighborhood hub and there you go
it's like pre-prepped pre like we can
decide what level we wanted at and work
backwards which what time and money we
have to involve in order to be able to
do that we can create solutions together
and I can see how we create the
solutions together but we need the
technology to create the solutions
together that are all technology
themselves mirrors within yours my
vision is especially since we're gonna
start with the healthcare app because I
need to get my health in order I need to
be able to feel like I'm doing what I
need to be doing which is eating better
and I'm not able to with my courage
spoons and resources and
I'm I need to be doing things that are
totally within my power melody that I
need but I need for some reason I'm not
doing them like I have nothing but time
and the ability to do yoga for an hour a
day like gentle not cardio yoga and that
would help my body immensely but I don't
do it I don't I don't have like
villainizing myself for that looking
down on myself for that isn't helpful in
any way does it make me do the yoga and
it also just adds more that I have
to deal with I need to know well how do
I do the thing that's cheap here easy
accessible and yet I'm still not doing
it and I know accountability with other
people I know possibly setting up a time
and doing with people on video whenever
there are tools we can create to help
each other stay on task and it's like
then that doesn't resonate with you and
you drop out of that group you find a
new way and everyone who finds a new way
to be able to excel at something they
previously weren't able to gets to offer
that not I don't need other people who
are like what do you mean anyway 10
hours ago again jaemin or take for two
hours and you can see the green and kale
smoothies and like just do it it's not
helpful to me cuz that has not worked in
my life and it definitely doesn't work
now when I have less ability for
patients in my like physical brain it's
like it wants to jump to other things
and do work differently than them and so
my vision instead of 8 minutes in is
that I want a bunch of neuro diapers
physically diverse intellectually
diverse humans that in this case have a
health struggle or a medical struggle
like a I have to deal with the medical
community is its own struggle being able
to create with and for that group of
people to create something we all want
to use by co-funding it and having a
voice in how it is how it is made and so
I want the board of directors to be
a bunch of people with health issues a
bunch of people who are neurodiverse a
bunch of people who are queer ER and
people of color and women and other
genders and I want like as diverse but I
want it from not the space of like oh we
need to fill this space in and we don't
have enough color on it we don't have
enough like from a space of like right
you as an individual bring all of that
to the table by being unique and so I
want uniqueness and uniqueness isn't
like let's fill in a quota uniqueness is
like this is a awesome human
being who brings all of their history
and all of their them to the table and
that involves their demographics as well
and if you look around and you're all
just a bunch of like rich white guys
which I'm probably not gonna be on that
board you have to act like why why
aren't really it's like oh cuz I have a
lot of rich white friends that are okay
like that's but let's reach outside the
social circle point we have to look at
if we're not attracting the people that
are diverse on the board but this brings
in diversity like the whole though what
I'm looking to create isn't let's get
people that look like business people
let's get let's get people that look
like our ablest capitalist societies
vision of success because the world
already works for those people and yet
it doesn't like it's all the way like if
you have to fake it to be that it's not
you you're being and so it's not
actually rewarding you it's rewarding
who you're pretending to be whereas if
you can be like yeah I'm awkward and I
stumble over words and I'm I'm wrong a
lot of the time there's a lot of wrong
knowledge and I had that's why I want to
get the like base of knowledge for us
all to look at where it is as easy as
googling who start in that movie
we don't need to argue about it it's
Google a whole and half a second I want
that to be for deliver literally every
day so that I have access to it so when
I do great question wait how do I know
that this is easy as looking that up
that's not like a mute button my brain
comes through yeah and I'm but get then
like my limited ability is to not be
able to actually recruit the people like
even one I'm really bad at inviting
people and being like you I want you on
my board not like hey do you happen to
maybe know someone who you might like to
anyway I want to contact this person
whose website it is and asked them as
well as their and their social circle
right and we have an amazing friend in
common I don't know how close this
friend is to them they are close to me
and I'm like when those things happen
and then I also saw this morning was
like my cousin my cousin who has had
nothing but with the medical
community and has her own physical
limitations and was the doula I was
involved like just I'm like right you're
amazing let's get you involved in this
project if she doesn't have other things
going on this is something that could be
going on as well which is what I this is
what I want going on like I want this
mission to move forward I want to have
something to work on with people who are
awesome I want the thing you're working
on to you also and want the people to be
awesome and I have the awesome idea I
just need the amazing people we're okay
with me saying awesome and amazing a lot
it's post the words clever enough type
and talk Pence is now 13 minute rush
people and then that like whoa great I
want to get involved that I get involved
I don't know I don't know
email me collaborative democracy it
gmail.com which I never checked but I
knew chuckling once every couple weeks
and then respond people if they respond
but no one responds then I know check it
but I know I need it separate from my
other one which is just full of junk
mail and stuff that I don't read until
respond see I need a different email to
keep separate the thing is I know he
don't respond to yes I need someone to
manage other people to get like email
lists and people don't want to get molds
and set up the time I'm like we'll meet
online we'll do it weekly but like
you've a picky to time does it work for
my brain like oh my brain works better
at this time but then other people
unavailable this time so pick a time and
then people don't anyway whatever
there's limitations that I have that are
medical that are mental
better everything in between personality
and we all have those and I think we can
create I know we can create a world that
works with that and not against that and
so working with people that already are
in a position in society the society
doesn't work for them and they don't
work for a society because of how
societies designed that it's ablest he
classist and not and all this is BS like
we can design something from within that
truly doesn't have those factors or
greatly minimizes that we still exist in
the world but you can't just mandate
that nobody makes racist thoughts and
nobody thinks homophobic thoughts
because people are homophobic and racist
we live in a society that is that so if
people to help people get out of that if
they want to and exist in a way that
doesn't negatively impact people who
that would negatively back well they're
living that their whole life or evolving
out of it he don't work like you don't
get to be a racist homophobic rich
asshole who changes all the laws to
support your homophobic
ways but nor do you get to starve to
death and being ostracized human because
you happen to have beliefs that your
brain fire is in that direction you're
mentally and emotionally there that's
all you're capable of we can't really
villainize people from not being capable
of mourner any more than I can go and
eyes myself by not being capable of more
that I will build an eyes myself from
being racist and homophobic I will
figure it out uncover it and figure it
the out but not the but like I
can't have more energy than I have I
can't have more less pain that I have
currently except when we create the
thing that does help me be able to do
that all right well I was just uh come
on and July came on printed live see how
this goes I hope have this microphone
helped somewhat I am in the process of
ordering one but that's daunting so I'm
figuring out which one is for the right
price point it's not even the money I
mean it is the body I'm not spending
hundreds of dollars on microphone but
like the 20 to 50 range I have no idea
right yeah
lighting so we're gonna work out it's
just like what it is I'm not gonna buy
lady
just funny because lighting I was in
different lighting but I don't think
lighting father's be on videos so I
don't took sound does sound us bothering
so I will try to wear this when I'm
doing it but also like you're like other
sounds and I don't know how much they
show up here and if I had the students
ivory watch this but I don't and I won't
Plus that I get self-conscious
so anyway end of livestream